Guide to the Duke University Chapel Recordings, 1954-2002 UA.17.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Recordings, 1954-2002; 1
  - James L. Price, Jr. - "Christian Faith and Learning", 1964 November 15; 262
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0273)
  - James T. Cleland - "Harvest Home", 1964 November 22; 263
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0274)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Deepen Your Spiritual Insight", 1964 November 29; 264
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0275)
  - Robert E. Cushman - "Promise and Judgment", 1964 December 06; 265
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0276)
  - Handel's Messiah Part I - conducted by Paul Young, 1964 December 07; 266
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 58, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-1170)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Image of God", 1964 December 13; 267
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0277)
  - O. Kelly Ingram - "Christmas and the New Humanity", 1964 December 20; 268
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0278)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "Calendar Watching", 1965 January 03; 269
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0279)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "A Strange Building Project", 1965 January 17; 270
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0280)
  - Edwin T. Dahlberg - "Truth before Freedom", 1965 January 24; 271
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0281)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Way at the River Kwai", 1965 January 31; 272
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 7, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0282)
  - Thomas A. Langford - "The Cruciality of the Cross", 1965 February 07; 273
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0283)
  - J. Russell Chandran - "The Upward Call of Christ", 1965 February 21; 274
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0284)
  - James T. Cleland - "Approaching Lent", 1965 February 28; 275
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0285)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Blind Eyes and Itching Ears", 1965 March 07; 276
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0286)
  - Franklin C. Fry - "God Sees", 1965 March 21; 277
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0287)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "A Tough New Breed of Servant - Minded Christians", 1965 March 28; 278
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0288)
  - John E. Hines - Palm Sunday Service, 1965 April 11; 279
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0289)
  - "The Words from the Cross: Seven Meditations" Good Friday Service Part 1, 1965 April 16; 280
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0290)
  - "The Words from the Cross: Seven Meditations" Good Friday Service Part 2, 1965 April 16; 281
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0291)
  - "The Words from the Cross: Seven Meditations" Good Friday Service Part 3, 1965 April 16; 282
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0292)
  - James T. Cleland - Easter Sermon, 1965 April 18; 283
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0293)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Honor Thy Father and Thy Mother", 1965 April 25; 284
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0294)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "Can We Forgive?", 1965 May 02; 285
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0295)
  - James T. Cleland - "Mother's Day?", 1965 May 09; 286
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0296)
  - Stuart C. Henry - "Laughter", 1965 May 16; 287
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0297)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "Honesty to God in Pulpit and Pew", 1965 May 23; 288
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0298)
  - Creighton Lacy - "The Path of Enlightened Compassion", 1965 May 30; 289
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0299)
  - Henry G. Ruark - "Power, Pride, and Peril", 1965 July 25; 290
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0300)
  - Warren Carr - "Crying over Spilled Wine", 1965 August 15; 291
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0301)
  - W. Wallace Fridy - "Life's Most Powerful Force", 1965 August 22; 292
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0302)
  - Funeral of Dr. Brainerd Currie - service by Wilkinson and Henderson, 1965 September 09; 293
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0303)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Discipline and Freedom", 1965 September 12; 294
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0304)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Duke University Chapel", 1965 September 19; 295
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0305)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "A Call for Fair Play", 1965 September 26; 296
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0306)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "Audacious Witness" Worldwide Communion Service, 1965 October 03; 297
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0307)
  - James T. Cleland - "Albert Schweitzer", 1965 October 10; 298
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0308)
  - Waldo Beach - "The Sacred and the Profane", 1965 October 17; 299
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0309)
  - Robert E. Cushman - "The Pope, the Council, and Religious Liberty", 1965 October 24; 300
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0310)
  - Samuel H. Miller - "Basic Simplicities", 1965 October 31; 301
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0311)
  - Samuel H. Miller - "On Hearing the Word", 1965 November 01; 302
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0312)
  - Samuel H. Miller - "On Seeing Miracles", 1965 November 02; 303
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0313)
  - James T. Cleland - All Saints Day Service, 1965 November 07; 304
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0314)
  - David H. C. Read - "Whose God Is Dead?", 1965 November 14; 305
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0315)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Thanksgiving Is Dangerous", 1965 November 21; 306
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0316)
  - Frank Baker - "Are You Dead or Alive?", 1965 November 28; 307
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0317)
  - Samuel Gandy - "Achieving a Living Faith", 1965 December 05; 308
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0318)
  - James T. Cleland - "God's Second Mile", 1965 December 12; 309
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0319)
  - M. Wilson Norbert, Jr. - "Christmas: Its Continuing Splendor", 1965 December 19; 310
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0320)
  - James T. Cleland - "Zechariah 14", 1966 January 09; 311
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 8, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0321)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Sam's Creek Revisited", 1966 January 16; 312
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0322)
  - Creighton Lacy - "A Social Creed in Poetry and Practice", 1966 January 23; 313
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0323)
  - Colin W. Williams - "Discipline and Discipleship", 1966 January 30; 314
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0324)
  - Boyd L. Daniels - "Is It I?", 1966 February 06; 315
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0325)
  - James T. Cleland - "Homo Sum, Christianus Sum", 1966 February 13; 316
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0326)
  - Ralph W. Sockman - "Wisdom for the Wilderness", 1966 February 20; 317
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0327)
  - Robert T. Osborn - "The Choice of the Church", 1966 February 27; 318
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0328)
  - Elton Trueblood - "Baptism by Fire", 1966 March 06; 319
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0329)
  - James T. Cleland - "Let Us Worship God", 1966 March 13; 320
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0330)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "On Being Sexually Right for the Right Reasons", 1966 March 20; 321
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0331)
  - Hugh Anderson - Maundy Thursday Communion Meditation, 1966 April 07; 322
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0332)
  - James T. Cleland - Easter Service, 1966 April 10; 323
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0333)
  - Edgar C. Reckard - "Good News Is No News", 1966 April 17; 324
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0334)
  - James L. Price, Jr. - "On Being a Christian in Today's World", 1966 April 24; 325
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0335)
  - Robert E. Cushman - "The Bell Tolls for Whom?", 1966 May 01; 326
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0336)
  - James T. Cleland - "Mater Mea", 1966 May 08; 327
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0337)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Examining the Examined Life", 1966 May 22; 328
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0338)
  - Thor Hall - "Let Religion Be Religious", 1966 May 29; 329
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0339)
  - Waldo Beach - "The Need for Roots"; Paul Knight - Baccalaureate Sermon, 1966 June 05; 330
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0340)
  - Daniel M. Schores - "Saints in the Shadows", 1966 June 12; 331
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0342)
  - Harry B. Partin - "The Language of His Hands", 1966 June 19, 1966 June 05; 332
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0343)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "Those Comforting Uncomfortable Words", 1966 July 10; 333
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0344)
  - James T. Cleland - "On Handling a Saint", 1966 July 17; 334
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0345)
  - H. Grady Hardin - "Morality: Old and New", 1966 July 24; 335
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0346)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "Forgiveness Plus", 1966 July 31; 336
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0347)
  - Harmon L. Smith, Jr. - "Sacrament and Social Action", 1966 August 07; 337
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0348)
  - Orval S. Wintermute - "A Faith in Creation", 1966 August 14; 338
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0349)
  - Charles P. Bowles - "The Unfinished Pyramid", 1966 August 21; 339
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0350)
  - D. Moody Smith, Jr. - "The Resurrection of the Dead", 1966 August 28; 340
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0351)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "The Grasshopper Attitude", 1966 September 04; 341
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0352)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "An Ordinary Disciple", 1966 September 11; 342
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0353)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Our World in New Perspective", 1966 September 18; 343
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0354)
  - Donald O. Soper - Opening Sunday, 1966 September 25; 344
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0355)
  - James T. Cleland - "Audacious Witness", 1966 October 02; 345
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0356)
  - Thomas E. McCollough - "Faith and Folly", 1966 October 16; 346
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0357)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Church in the World", 1966 October 23; 347
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0358)
  - Bishop Earl G. Hunt, Jr. - "New Testament Christianity", 1966 October 30; 348
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0359)
  - John D. Maguire - "The Resurrection of God", 1966 November 06; 349
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 9, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0360)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "You May Have Already Won", 1966 November 13; 350
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0361)
  - James T. Cleland - "Sermon for Thanksgiving", 1966 November 20; 351
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0362)
  - Donald J. Welch - "Dormez Vous?", 1966 November 27; 352
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0363)
  - L. Harold DeWolf - "Three Whys", 1966 December 04; 353
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0364)
  - James T. Cleland - "Our Rememberable Day" Founders' Day, 1966 December 11; 354
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0365)
  - Wesley Aitkin - "An Old and Tested Remedy", 1966 December 25; 355
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0366)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "The Art of Decision Making", 1967 January 08; 356
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0367)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "A Renewed Church for Spaceship Earth?", 1967 January 15; 357
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0368)
  - Thomas A. Langford - "To Pick up the Wrong Bag", 1967 January 22; 358
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0369)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson and Joe F. Harris - "Situation Ethics", 1967 January 29; 359
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0370)
  - D. Moody Smith, Jr. - Communion Meditation, 1967 February 05; 360
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0371)
  - Milton H. Robinson - "Beyond the Tropic of Cancer", 1967 February 26; 361
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0372)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson and Dennis M. Campbell - "The Perfect Crime", 1967 March 05; 362
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0373)
  - William Sloan Coffin, Jr. - "Burdened with Erudition and Paralyzed with Indecision: A Sermon on Learned Paralytics", 1967 March 12; 363
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0374)
  - James T. Cleland - "Triumph and Tears", 1967 March 19; 364
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0375)
  - James T. Cleland - "He Is Not Here, but Is Risen" Easter Service, 1967 March 26; 365
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0376)
  - David G. Bradley - "Christ the Pattern", 1967 April 02; 366
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0377)
  - Waldo Beach - "Divided Minds and a Single Heart", 1967 April 09; 367
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0378)
  - James T. Cleland - "Somewhere There Is Who Doesn't Love a Wall", 1967 April 16; 368
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0379)
  - John Garrett - "Struggle with God", 1967 April 23; 369
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0380)
  - Stuart C. Henry - "Prisoner of Grace", 1967 April 30; 370
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0381)
  - Evans E. Crawford - "A Message for the Left - Hand", 1967 May 07; 371
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0382)
  - Richard A. Goodling - "Rediscovering the Family", 1967 May 14; 372
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0383)
  - James T. Cleland - "God in Three Persons?", 1967 May 21; 373
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0384)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Discipline and Freedom", 1967 May 28; 374
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0385)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "Then and Now", 1967 June 04; 375
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0386)
  - Donald Mackay - "Who Is I AM?", 1967 June 18; 376
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0387)
  - H. Eugene Peacock - "When God Hides His Face", 1967 June 25; 377
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0388)
  - James T. Cleland - "Grace, Repentance, and Reconciliation", 1967 July 02; 378
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0389)
  - O. Kelly Ingram - "Christian Righteousness - - 1967", 1967 July 09; 379
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0390)
  - James T. Cleland - "Style and Front", 1967 July 16; 380
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0391)
  - Harry B. Partin - "Christian Solidarity", 1967 July 23; 381
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0392)
  - Thomas A. Langford - Communion Meditation, 1967 July 30; 382
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0393)
  - Thor Hall - "A Choice Concern", 1967 August 06; 383
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0394)
  - D. Moody Smith, Jr. - "Violence - As American as Cherry Pie?", 1967 August 13; 384
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0395)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Strange Bedfellows", 1967 August 20; 385
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0396)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "The Power of Imagination", 1967 September 03; 386
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0397)
  - Carl C. James - "The Motivators", 1967 September 10; 387
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 10, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0398)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Ding an Sich", 1967 September 17; 388
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0399)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Chapel in the University", 1967 September 24; 389
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0400)
  - D. Jürgen Moltmann - Communion Meditation, 1967 October 01; 390
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0401)
  - Carlyle Marney - "The God of This Twilight", 1967 October 08; 391
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0402)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Centurion at the Cross", 1967 October 15; 392
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0403)
  - Hans J. Hillerbrand - "Anniversary Toast to a Heretic", 1967 October 29; 393
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0404)
  - Bishop John E. Hines - Convocation, 1967 November 01; 394
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0405)
  - Creighton Lacy - "A Himalayan View of Christianity", 1967 November 05; 395
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0406)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Reflections on a Duke Chronicle", 1967 November 19; 396
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0407)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Advent of Sin", 1967 December 03; 397
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0408)
  - Albert C. Outler - "So What Have You Done for Me Lately?", 1967 December 10; 398
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0409)
  - McMurry S. Richey - "The Sovereign Might and Utter Vulgarity of God", 1967 December 17; 399
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0410)
  - W. Arthur Kale - "Risk - Taking and Peace - Making", 1967 December 24; 400
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0411)
  - Thor Hall - "Another Year", 1967 December 31; 401
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0412)
  - Philip A. Johnson - "The Fall of Infallibility", 1968 January 07; 402
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0413)
  - James T. Cleland - "The Race That Is Set before Us", 1968 January 14; 403
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0414)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "Robert Burns and the Religion - Government Controversy", 1968 January 21; 404
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0415)
  - Stuart C. Henry - "Religion for a Yeoman", 1968 January 28; 405
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0416)
  - Wesley P. Aitkin - "Safe on Home - Base", 1968 February 04; 406
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0417)
  - Elton Trueblood - "The Paradox of Greatness", 1968 February 11; 407
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0418)
  - James T. Cleland - "My Name Is Jim C.: I Am a Sinner", 1968 February 25; 408
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0419)
  - Howard C. Wilkinson - "The Existence of a Personal God", 1968 March 03; 409
    - Original 1/4-inch open reel audio tape (Box 11, Audio-reel UA.17.01.0003 RR-0420)
  - Roy D. Nichols - "The Promised Land", 1968 March 10; 410